<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<dunes-script-module name="cloneVM" result-type="VC:Task" api-version="6.0.0" id="b3dbd680-b951-4cbc-be93-395c8c05b1ed" version="0.2.1" allowed-operations="vf" category-name="com.vmware.library.vc.basic">
  <description><![CDATA[Creates a clone of this virtual machine. If the virtual machine is used as a template, this method corresponds to the deploy command. 
Any % (percent) character used in this name parameter must be escaped, unless it is used to start an escape sequence. Clients may also escape any other characters in this name parameter. 
The privilege required on the source virtual machine depends on the source and destination types: 
	- source is virtual machine, destination is virtual machine - VirtualMachine.Provisioning.Clone 
	- source is virtual machine, destination is template - VirtualMachine.Provisioning.CreateTemplateFromVM
	- source is template, destination is virtual machine - VirtualMachine.Provisioning.DeployTemplate 
	- source is template, destination is template - VirtualMachine.Provisioning.CloneTemplate 
If customization is requested in the CloneSpec, then the VirtualMachine.Provisioning.Customize privilege must also be held on the source virtual machine.]]></description>
  <param n="vm" t="VC:VirtualMachine"><![CDATA[The Source Virtual Machine or Template for the Clone Operation]]></param>
  <param n="vmFolder" t="VC:VmFolder"><![CDATA[The location of the new virtual machine.]]></param>
  <param n="name" t="string"><![CDATA[The name of the new virtual machine.]]></param>
  <param n="powerOn" t="boolean"><![CDATA[Specifies whether or not the new VirtualMachine should be powered on after creation.]]></param>
  <param n="template" t="boolean"><![CDATA[Specifies whether or not the new virtual machine should be marked as a template.]]></param>
  <param n="datastore" t="VC:Datastore"><![CDATA[The datastore where the virtual machine should be located. If not specified, the current datastore is used. ]]></param>
  <param n="host" t="VC:HostSystem"><![CDATA[The datastore where the virtual machine should be located. If not specified, the current datastore is used.]]></param>
  <param n="pool" t="VC:ResourcePool"><![CDATA[The resource pool to which this virtual machine should be attached.]]></param>
  <param n="thinProvisioned" t="boolean"><![CDATA[If true, the VM disk size unused are not reserved on the datastore]]></param>
  <script encoded="false"><![CDATA[var transform = null;
if (thinProvisioned == true) {
	transform = VcVirtualMachineRelocateTransformation.sparse;
} else if (thinProvisioned == false) {
	transform = VcVirtualMachineRelocateTransformation.flat;
}

if (datastore == null) {
	datastore = vm.datastore[0];
}
relocateSpec = System.getModule("com.vmware.library.vc.vm.spec").getRelocateSpec(datastore,null,host,pool,transform);
cloneSpec = System.getModule("com.vmware.library.vc.vm.spec").getCloneSpec(null,null,relocateSpec,powerOn,template);





return vm.cloneVM_Task(vmFolder, name, cloneSpec);]]></script>
</dunes-script-module>